[{"answer": "Well, yes.  I suppose I am a bit anxious", "docId": "mission-impossible-2_shoot.txt", "asentId": 3, "question": " I'm with an old friend now, my friend", "qsentId": 2}, {"answer": "No.  Should I", "docId": "mission-impossible-2_shoot.txt", "asentId": 5, "question": "No.  Just as if I'd like to", "qsentId": 4}, {"answer": " Lovely.  Who are you and what's it going to cost me", "docId": "mission-impossible-2_shoot.txt", "asentId": 7, "question": "Do what", "qsentId": 6}, {"answer": "Oh.  Well..this isn't exactly by the book", "docId": "mission-impossible-2_shoot.txt", "asentId": 9, "question": "They've got a book for everything", "qsentId": 8}, {"answer": " Sorry I barged in on your vacation", "docId": "mission-impossible-2_shoot.txt", "asentId": 11, "question": "Don't be.  Wouldn't be on vacation if you did", "qsentId": 10}, {"answer": "Well.  You're sorry and I'm sorry", "docId": "mission-impossible-2_shoot.txt", "asentId": 13, "question": "Like what", "qsentId": 12}, {"answer": "Then makes sure she continues to see him. Gets him confide in her and report to you", "docId": "mission-impossible-2_shoot.txt", "asentId": 15, "question": "Well, then I mislead you.  Or you made the wrong assumption.  Either way we're asking her to resume a prior relationship, not do anything she hasn't already done", "qsentId": 14}, {"answer": "Well, then I mislead you.  Or you made the wrong assumption.  Either way we're asking her to resume a prior relationship, not do anything she hasn't already done", "docId": "mission-impossible-2_shoot.txt", "asentId": 17, "question": "Go to bed with a man and lie to him? She's a woman.  She's got all the training she needs", "qsentId": 16}, {"answer": "How's it going?  Everything okay", "docId": "mission-impossible-2_shoot.txt", "asentId": 19, "question": "Just like old times", "qsentId": 18}, {"answer": "my friend that", "docId": "mission-impossible-2_shoot.txt", "asentId": 21, "question": "Left jacket pocket confirmed", "qsentId": 20}, {"answer": "Sort it all out", "docId": "mission-impossible-2_shoot.txt", "asentId": 23, "question": "A change of plans", "qsentId": 22}, {"answer": "Fatigued, certainly.  But dead is a little extreme.  On the other hand, when me dear my friend had your pulse and blood pressure he has less than ten hours to live", "docId": "mission-impossible-2_shoot.txt", "asentId": 25, "question": "You are infected with  my friend", "qsentId": 24}, {"answer": "Yes, I believe that's right", "docId": "mission-impossible-2_shoot.txt", "asentId": 27, "question": "You mean that leaves Miss Hall", "qsentId": 26}]